(funky intro music)
♪ In the not too
distant future, ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13, ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester
and TV's Frank, ♪
♪ Were hatching
an evil scheme. ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike, ♪
♪ Just a regular Joe
they didn't like. ♪
♪ Their experiment needed
a good test case, ♪
♪ So they conked
him on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot
him into space. ♪
- [Mike] Let me down!
♪ We'll send him
cheesy movies, ♪
♪ The worst we can find. ♪
♪ La la la. ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all, ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind. ♪
♪ Now keep in mind, ♪
♪ Mike can't control, where
the movies begin or end. ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends. ♪
♪ (mechanical noise) ♪
♪ Robot roll call. ♪
♪ Cambot. ♪
♪ Gypsy. ♪
♪ Tom Servo. ♪
♪ Crow. ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes, ♪
♪ And other science facts, ♪
♪ La la la. ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself,
It's just a show. ♪
♪ I should really just relax. ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000.♪
(clattering and doors closing)
- [Mike] See, I don't
know what my area code is
cause I'm up in the milky
way, for crying out loud.
(chuckling)
- [Tom Servo] Oh, hi, everyone.
Tom Servo here on the
Satellite of Love.
And this is my pal, Crow.
- [Crow] Yeah, and that
goofy looking guy back there,
that's Mike Nelson.
He's trying to call his
grandma on the phone.
It's a sweet gesture, isn't it?
But we explained to him,
It's not that easy to do when
you're stranded in space.
- Yeah, well you
guys were never on
with a stack of calling cards
and a few little
tricks like I am.
- [Cow And Tom Servo] Wow.
- [Tom Servo] Cool.
I gotta see this.
- [Mike] Hey, get
around here. This is it.
(telephone ringing)
- [Tom Servo] You're kidding.
You actually get your
grandma on the phone?
Well, grandma's a mall walker.
She's probably just
getting in right now.
- [Grandma] Yello.
- Hello. Grandma, this is Mike.
I'm stranded in space.
You got to help.
You've got to get
someone to help me down.
- [Grandma] What?
What's that? Speak up.
- I say, I've been
shanghaied on a satellite.
You've got to get someone
to help me get outta here.
- [Grandma] I'm just kidding.
This is Catherine and
I'm not in right now.
I might be sitting
for Tommy's kids,
or else I'm at Linda's.
Leave a message.
(beep)
- Grandma, listen very
carefully. This is Mike.
I've been stra-
(beep)
- That was my only chance.
- [Tom Servo] Wow.
That's harsh, huh?
- [Crow] That's okay, Mike.
We're your family now.
- Yeah.
(dial tones)
(fun music)
- [Tom Servo] Sprint. No.
- [Crow] Mike, Mike, Mike, Mike.
Oh, you should
really make a note
of that you got a machine
so that if the bill comes
and we're erroneously
charged for the call,
then you have a paperwork
to back up your claim
that you are charged
for the call in error
so that you won't have to
pay for that call, Mike.
- [Tom Servo] Crow,
you lived during the great
depression, didn't you?
- [Crow] Oh, Back rack
and David are calling.
- [Mike] They are?
- [Crow] Just push the button.
- [Dr. Forrester]
Laundry and laundry.
Oh, Mike. You would not
believe the day I've had.
I don't know how
single parents do it.
Oh, I was excited with the
arrival of young Frank.
- [Frank] Dr. F, come on.
- Clayton's on the
phone right now, Frank.
It's a 25 hour a day job,
keeping track of Frank.
He's into everything.
Sometimes I think we
both need a little break.
That's why I've invented
the Frank Enforcer.
You, see the Frank Enforcer
keeps little Frank suspended
in that disorienting
no man's land
between floor and ceiling.
The mat with the
nails jutting out
at a most dangerous angle,
gently discourages
Frank from jumping out
of the Frank Enforcer
and into Dr. F's hair.
Just a little minute,
Frankie. There you go.
Now, Dr. Forrester
has time to tabulate
and standardize results
of our latest experiment,
postulate new theories or
just get the laundry done,
without worrying about this one.
Plus, I've gotten to know
someone very special. Me.
Got to go, Mike.
We get fussy if we've been in
there more than a few weeks.
Immature little baby.
- [Crow] I'm guessing Frank's
in the 90th percentile.
- [Tom Servo] Anyway, let
me set the scene here.
You're at your favorite
candle-lit restaurant,
spending time with
someone, very special.
Exchanging lingering
glances over the fettuccine.
- [Crow] What?
- [Tom Servo] Laughing
low throaty laughs
over a shared private
joke, fingers entwined.
- [Crow] Would you just
get on with it, Servo?
- [Tom Servo] And
sometimes you just need
your server's attention.
Enter the Waiter Baiter.
(laughing)
- [Mike] I'll be right
over here. Hi, Ted!
- [Crow] Don't waste
your valuable time
trying to get your
waiter's attention.
Let the Waiter Baiter
do the dirty work.
- [Mike] I'll be with
you in a moment, please.
I'm in the weeds here.
- [Tom Servo] So what
are we gonna have here?
- [Crow] Oh, I think
I'll get the haggis.
- [Tom Servo] Oh, let's
split that why don't we?
- [Crow] Yeah. Split the gut.
- [Mike] Okay. Well,
what, what do...
What do you think sir?
(Frank laughing)
- [Dr. Forrester] I think
you'll be having our special,
a tough stringy antre called,
Teenage strangler.
Frank!
Served with a distasteful,
little appetizer,
about love or some such slop.
Frank!
I think I'm going to have
to put Frank down for nap.
Permanently.
Frank!
(Frank laughing loudly)
- [Tom Servo] No no, you
had three big bites of my
lettuce wedge.
- [Crow] Yeah, but you had my
clean beets, so it evens out.
- [Tom Servo] I only
had a little taste
of your clean beets.
- [Crow] You ate the whole half.
- [Tom Servo] I'm not going
to pay for your clean beets.
- [Crow] Well I'm not going
to have to pay for it.
- [Mike] Ladies. Ladies.
(alarm blaring)
We have movie sign!
- [Crow And Tom Servo]
Oh my god, Movie sign!
(doors opening)
- [Mike] Wish you
too would of just,
get together and paid the tab.
- [Tom Servo] Is this love?
Or is it just rough sex with
Micheal Douglas?
- [Crow] Wow.
- [Mike] By Paul H. Landis,
who has never known
the touch of a woman.
- [Crow] Collaborator,
Lillian Bilkey,
who's single and lives
in a furnished room
with six cats.
- Lillian Milky.
- Bilkey.
- Milky.
- [Mike] Well, except for
Tom Hanks and Peter Scolari.
- [Tom Servo] (heavy
panting) Out of my way,
I want to catch the end of
Bobby Heck's trumpet solo.
- [Crow] Ms. Channing.
There's an Eve Harrington
here to see you.
- [Mike] It look's like
Van Gogh's Room in Au rel.
- [Tom Servo] So
um... where's Waldo?
- [Mike] Uh, he's under the bed.
- [Crow] Geez. How many
times was she held back?
(chuckling)
- Hi Peg.
- [Mike] Hi mom.
- Wow. You look more excited
than I've ever seen you before,
and that's saying something.
(Crow making cat noises)
- Oh Liz, you'll never guess.
I got engaged to Joe.
We're going to be married
at the end of the semester.
Right after Joe graduates.
- What?
But you've only been going
steady with him for a couple of
months.
- Exactly. Three
months and three days.
- [Tom servo] Love has
made me anal. Hehe.
- Peg, are you gonna drop
out of college before you
graduate? I mean, you've
only got another year to go.
- Oh Liz, everyone isn't
as slow as you and Andy.
- [Crow] Besides,
you're a Romulan.
- I want to get married in June.
- [Mike] Hmm, get the cuffs.
- Joe's been told he
has a good chance of
getting a job on a pro
football team this summer.
- [Crow] As a water boy.
- Are you going to phone your
mom and dad about getting
engaged?
- [Crow] Actually
they're married already.
- I'm scared stiff at
what mother was say,
she'll raise the roof.
I think I sent a
telegram instead.
- Don't be silly Peg.
You always talk as though
your mother was an ogre.
- [Mike] I've known
her for 50 years.
- Mother will be furious.
Every so often to writes to
ask if I've seen Pete Standin.
You know, just
because his father's a
big time real estate man.
And he's mother's idea
of a perfect catch.
- [Tom Servo] He just got
the Glen Garret count.
- Compared to Joe,
Pete's so dull.
Joe's so handsome.
- [Crow] Handsome
equals not dull.
- Honestly Peg,
I don't know how many times
ever since we were in high
school together,
I've heard you go on the same
way about some men or other.
- Oh but this is
different Liz, really.
- [Mike] He's at atomically
correct and everything.
- It's a real thing.
- I remember when I first
felt that way about Andy.
- [Tom Servo] At the
turn of the century.
- I think about
him all the time.
Gosh, Peggy, you just
can't rush into marriage.
- [Crow] Why not?
Julia Roberts did.
- Don't mind my saying this.
- [Mike] Uh oh.
- You and Andy seems so, so...
- So old fashioned,
I suppose you mean?
- [Mike] No, just old.
- You've been going together
for a year and a half.
last month you finally
became engaged.
I'm just not like that.
- [Tom Servo] I'm easy. Hehe.
- That's fine. But, are you
sure you'll always be in love
like you are now?
- [Tom Servo] With
somebody, sure.
- Liz, how can you
say such a thing?
- Oh, wait a minute, Peg,
please don't get upset.
All I mean is, are you
sure you see eye to eye
about things like...
- [Tom Servo] The trade deficit.
- Well, like,
money and children?
- [Tom Servo] Bogus.
- What's right and what's wrong.
How do you get along with
each other's families?
- [Mike] Boring.
- Suppose your
parents won't approve.
You have to think
about these things Peg.
- [Crow] Look, can
we get separate beds?
- As far as I'm concerned,
you don't have to think if
you've found the right man.
- [Tom Servo] Excuse me,
but that's my boyfriend.
- You better go and
send that telegram.
- [Mike] I'm too much in
love to send a telegram.
- [Crow] I love his picture.
Maybe someday I'll
meet him in person.
- [Tom Servo] Let's
see if my, yeah.
If my, if my demands are not
met the screens of those who've
wronged me in the smell of
burning flesh will fill the
student, union.
- How's the essay coming?
- [Mike] Not so good mom.
- Page two? Not so good.
- [Crow] Will you just lay off.
- I can do an engineering
paper in two days Liz.
I've been working on
this english assignment
for a week and
nothing.
- Gosh, Andy,
you got to get your English
or you won't graduate.
- [Crow] Would you
just leave me alone.
- Look, why don't we meet
at the library tonight?
- [Crow] Oh yeah.
- Maybe I can help.
- Gee, thanks Liz,
that'd be swell of you.
- [Mike] Conforms
without a cause.
- Hey look, the
lovebirds have arrived.
- [Crow] And they're
leaving their droppings
all over the place. Hehe.
- Nothing like advertising.
- They got engaged last night.
(dramatic gasping)
- Peggy said they're getting
married right after commence.
- Marriage?
- [Tom Servo] It's immoral.
- Boy, Peggy thinks
it's all handholding
and gazing into
each other's eyes.
- [Mike] She doesn't know
about the stench of ammonia
from the piles of
crap filled diapers.
- You were like that once too.
- [Crow] And now, a firm
and hardy hand clap.
- Those first dates
were exciting.
The more I got to know you,
the more I liked what I knew.
Though, I suppose I was
really intrigued by the
things I didn't know about you.
- [Tom Servo] Like you
being a communist and all.
- we seem to have lots
in common, didn't we?
There was so many things
we could do together.
- [Mike] What the
hell was that for?
You were supposed to cover
down a line. I told you.
Come here, look at that.
- I wish I could
argue with you there.
- [Crow] But you've
emasculated me.
- You really enjoy a
good argument, don't you?
I haven't forgotten the time
the Dean's rule on drinking
came out.
- [Tom Servo] I can
quit anytime I want to.
- That was the day I found out
we could argue like anything
and somehow love
each other more.
I thought expulsion was
too stiff a penalty,
one small slip and some guy's
whole life could be changed.
- [Mike] Drinking in college?
I never heard of that.
- Andy, but I couldn't
entirely agree.
Expelling somebody is a
serious thing of course, but,
so is drinking in a dorm.
All those people living
so close together.
- [Crow] Look would you just
lay off for ten seconds.
- Well we didn't
settle the issue,
but it sure was fun trying.
I wanted to convince you
and you try to convince me.
I guess we became most
convinced about each other.
- We must have,
up until a month ago, that
finger look kind of bare.
You remember?
- [Tom Servo] Naked.
- [Crow] Zirconia, that jerk.
- [Mike] QVC. Thank you.
- [Tom Servo] Uh, I figured
if like we split it,
the cost, we can afford it.
- [Crow] Gifts, given in
dorms, punished by expulsion.
- [Tom Servo] ] Hmm, you
tastes like Jean Kirkpatrick.
- [Mike] Oh I'm on fire,
enough. That's enough.
- [Crow] Honey, I also
got you a subscription to
modern maturity.
- Gosh, I think our folks
were even more excited
than we were.
- [Mike] Yeah, when your
dad got the shotgun down.
- Ready to go back to the dorm?
- Hi.
- Hey, congratulations you
too. I just heard the news.
- Oh thanks Andy.
(funky music)
- Have you found a place
to live around here?
- Oh, I don't think we
have to worry about it.
Can we just find a little
apartment somewhere.
- Peggy.
- [Crow] It's the heat, run.
- Hi darling.
- [Mike] Oh poopey.
- What are you doing here?
- We've got your telegram.
- Aren't you thrilled?
- Should we be?
- Now don't be crossed Betty.
Let's hear Peggy's side.
- [Mike] Well, he's
good in the sack and
he likes to get high.
- Well, we've been going steady
for over three months now.
Mother, dad, we have such
a wonderful time together.
- [Tom Servo] Oh my god.
- I'm in love, really in
love for the first time.
we planned to marry
right after commencement,
it's as simple as that.
- [Crow] You're grounded.
- Peggy, you wrote us
last week that Joe was
going into
professional football,
has he signed on
with any team yet?
- Well, no, he hasn't
got a contract yet,
but he's been told he's a very
good chance of getting one,
after all, he's been the star
of our team here this year,
you know?
- Peg, your mother and
I have come down here
to ask you to put
off your wedding.
- [Tom Servo] And to kill Joe.
- At least after
you've graduated.
Now, dear, if you'll wait,
we can help you get a house
and you can set up a home
properly.
- [Crow] Take the house.
- [Mike And Tom
Servo] Take the house.
- Dad, I love Joe.
- [Tom Servo] Kill
us, please kill us.
- We can live in
a little apartment
wherever we're situated.
Being with Joe means more
to me than anything else.
And we won't wait.
- But dear,
You only have one year
and a month more to go.
It be such a pity
not to finish here.
- [Mike] Captain Spalding.
- And while your
finishing last year,
Joe can get established
in football.
If that's what he really wants.
And you'll have some more time
to see if you're right for
each other.
- That theoretical
stuff, gives me a pain.
We're sure now we're
right for each other.
And that's all that's
really important.
- Peggy, we want to meet Joe.
Now look,
- [Tom Servo] Don't dear.
- Why don't we all have
dinner together at the hotel
tonight?
And then he can tell us all
about this football business.
- Football is Joe's
profession, mother,
and it's just as good
as anything else.
- [Crow] Get a rope, honey.
- Joe and I had already
made plans for a
date tonight and I see no
reason to change them now.
- But Peggy Dear-
- Your not going to
stop us marrying.
Dad thinks all we have to do
is pay for something and he'll
get his own way.
- [Tom Servo] Worked till now.
- You think by treating
me like a child,
you can force me to
do what you want.
You're both wrong.
I'm no child, I'm me
and I'll do what I want.
- [Mike] Well honey, it looks
likely spawned a demon seed.
- Don't worry, Betty.
She'll get over it. Just
a touch of hysterics,
that's all, why by the time
the end of the semester comes,
she'll probably be madly
in love with someone else.
Come on. We will see her
again in the morning.
- [Crow] Let's hit the
bar it's happy hour.
- [Tom Servo] Young
Colonel Sanders.
- [Mike] There's
no football player.
It might be in
the swing fighter.
- Oh Joe, I'm so mixed
up about everything.
- [Crow] Original
or extra crispy?
- Folks trying to stop us.
They've always tried
to run my life.
- [Mike] I want
you to run my life.
- Like when I wanted to go
to a dance at a Roadhouse.
Dad insisted that
I stay at home.
- [Mike] Just cause
Patrick Swayze was there.
- I was so mad, I
climbed out of a window
and went to a
girlfriend's house.
- [Mike] That's
kind of odd, honey.
- And my folks were frantic.
They looked all over from me.
Even called the police.
- [Crow] Finally found
me at that crack house.
- What a girl.
I had so many brothers and
sisters, nobody to miss me,
if I left them.
- [Tom Servo] Oh
who cares about you?
- Take a couple of days for
anyone to realize I'd gone.
- And believe me being an only
child has its disadvantages.
(making honing noises)
- In college has
been sheer heaven.
- [Mike] except for the classes.
- Joe we've got to do something.
They'll do anything
to break us up.
I wish I hadn't sent that
telegram, if Liz hadn't made me.
- Look honey.
- [Tom Servo] I should
tell you. I'm a woman.
- I love you.
I want to marry you.
- [Tom Servo] But
what is this crap?
- I love you too Joe.
I don't ever want
to be away from you.
- [Crow] We have a winner.
- [Tom Servo] Luminary
returns indicate love.
- [Mike] He's at the 40, the 50.
He might go all the way.
- [Crow] You tastes
like Troy Donahue.
- [Tom servo] You taste
like Eleanor Donahue.
- [Mike] Oh, I'm spent,
it was incredible.
- We'll work something out.
- [Tom Servo] Watch
out for snakes.
- [Crow] Meanwhile,
back in the cold bitter
Loveless life of her parents.
- Well, good morning Liz.
- Good morning, Mr. Kramer.
Good morning Mrs. Kramer.
Good morning Liz.
- We inquired at the
desk for Peggy, but
they said she wasn't
in. So we asked for you.
- [Crow] We knew you'd be in.
- I don't really
know Mr. Kramer.
She left the room very early
this morning before I was
awake.
- [Mike] For some reason,
she took her Teddy.
- She left this note for me.
- [Tom Servo] Dear
dad, lose the mustache.
You twisted old fruit.
- Dear Liz. I'm afraid.
Mother and dad would
try to stop us.
So Joe and I left this
morning to be married.
- [Crow] Oh Mr. Drivesdale oh.
- Break news to the folks.
Try to explain that this
is something I had to do.
I'm afraid. They
won't understand.
Love Peggy.
- [Tom Servo] Here.
Look at it. Look at it.
- I'm sorry Mrs. Kramer.
- [Crow] Got the
boogers again eh dear.
- Couldn't she have told
us how she really felt.
She only mentioned
this boy twice and..
- [Mike] Look I'm
the roommate lay off.
- I just thought it was
another college crush.
- How could she do it?
- [Tom Servo] Well, see, the
man lies next to the woman.
- Getting married at the end
of the semester would have been
better than eloping.
Poor darling.
- [Crow] Ah, let's make sweet
love and have a new daughter.
- She may have so
much to regret.
- [Mike] She could
end up like us.
- [Crow] Sorry. I
can't be your daughter.
I already have parents.
Bye-bye.
Geez, I don't blame Peggy.
What a couple of wing nuts.
- [Mike] All right, let's
go talk about our superior
relationship.
- [Announcer] Liz and Andy.
Are they really in love?
- [Tom Servo] Can love
transcendent gender.
- A year and a half now.
Is Peggy right in
thinking that Andy and Liz
are too old fashioned.
- [Crow] Is this
going to be on a test?
- What about Peggy and Joe?
they appear to be in love.
They obviously are physically
attracted to one another.
Right now they're radiant with
excitement and the thrill of
taking matters into
their own hands.
When this excitement of
the moment settles down.
What will remain?
- [Tom Servo] A big visa bill.
- Will they be companions
as well as lovers?
Willing and able to
share the realities and
responsibilities of having a
home, bringing up children and
making a living.
- [Crow] Hey, you're
bringing me down, man.
- Really no one and
only for any of us.
Until we make it so
by our own choice.
And when we do choose,
we have to know,
will this love stand
the test of time.
- [Tom Servo] You make the call.
- How would you answer this
question for Liz and Andy?
Peggy and Joe.
- [Crow] Bob and
Carol. Ted and Elise.
- Is this love?
- [Crow] You have 10 minutes
to answer the
questions starting now.
- [Mike] And now,
stay tuned for the Clarence
Thomas Anita hill herring.
- [Tom Servo] No
animals, were hurt,
during the filming
of this movie.
(whistling the tune)
- [Tom Servo] How
much affection?
- [Crow] When should I marry?
- [Mike] Know your ointments.
- [Tom Servo] What's
that down there?
- [Crow] When he wants it rough.
- [Mike] Procreation,
not recreation.
- [Tom Servo] Oh, no pleasure.
- [Crow] McClintock.
(doors closing)
- Then shall I turn my face and
hear one bird, sing terribly
afar, in the lost
lands. Now that,
my little friends, is love.
- [Tom Servo] Oh.
Not since Edgar Allen
Poe's love for the
calmly Helen Chronicle
so eloquently.
Have I been so moved. So taken.
- [Crow And Tom Servo] So
- [Crow] Bored.
- [Mike] Hey, come on Crow,
that's one of my all
time favorite poems.
It's so complete in its beauty.
Let me read you some more.
- That ain't love.
How can it be?
It's unrequited.
Plus it's got all that
longing and yearning junk.
I want to hear about hot
love, quick and ready.
You know, see it,
like it. Got it.
- Oh, like Rod Stewart
sees Rachel Hunter on TV,
rights her a letter and
then boom. They're married.
- Yeah. You think that's love?
- Oh, it is for me. Have
you've seen that video.
Wow. Hehe
- I'm serious.
Do you think it's love? Or how
about Eddie Gourmet and Steve
Lawrence, is that love true?
- Well, it's love,
but it's not love on the scale
of Glen Campbell and Tanya
Tucker.
- Oh no.
- Well, how about
Emilio and Paula?
Is she forever his girl or
is he a cold-hearted snake?
- Oh, Crow.
She's so cute. And he's
just as nice as the Dickens.
I'm sure it can survive. We'll
just look at Don and Melanie.
Hey, no problems there, huh?
- True.
Or how about Bruce and Demi?
- Joanne and Paul.
Oh, and Kurt Cobain
and Courtney Love.
Now they've built their
house on high solid ground.
- And there's the classic
Eddie Adams and Ernie Kovacs.
- Maria Chriver and Arnold.
- Jack Douglas and Rico.
Hey John and Yoko
for that matter.
- Joan Didion and
John Gregory Done.
- Get with it Nelson,
showbiz love is the
only love that matters.
- Oh it is huh? Okay.
Well then how about
Burton and Lonnie?
(Tom Servo gasping)
- Oh no, I can't believe
it. Please. It's so sad.
Oh, who would have guessed.
Oh an there little boy.
And what will become
of the dinner theater?
(Tom Servo crying)
- Oh, good one Nelson.
- Like walking on
eggshells with this one.
- Eggshells no.
(funky music)
- Hey, Lugi jamming
with Ramsey Lewis.
- I'm getting more afraid.
Every time I come to
meet you here.
- Who's ever gonna find us
here at school? And anyway,
where else can we go
at night to be alone?
Don't worry.
- I am worried. Jimmy.
I'm afraid of something.
I don't know what it is.
- Afraid. Of who?
- [Tom Servo] Richard
Speck on a date.
- Your folks will never know,
as long as they think
you're with Ann.
- [Mike] Does Ann do this?
- [Crow] Forbidden
love is the best.
- [Mike] Damn him, damn him.
- [Tom Servo] You can hear
the ocean roar in this film.
- [Mike] You're almost
done with my boyfriend?
- Come on.
- [Mike] More tongue.
- It's late, I gotta go home.
- [Mike] Mel, kiss my grits.
- Betty, will you-
- Okay, Okay, I'll
be right there.
Let's go, no more. I'll see you.
- [Crow] Go on, get.
- I'm sorry Ann, oh,
hello Mr. Wilson.
What are you doing
here? It's so late.
- I might ask you the same
question, young ladies.
- [Crow] Let me
check my line here.
- Shouldn't be out
this time of night.
- [Tom Servo] Time of night.
- Or anytime at night
when the school is closed.
- Look I'll walk you
home. Oh wait right here.
I'll be right back in a minute.
I'll get my hat and coat,
turn off the lights,
I'll be right back.
- No, no, no.
You don't have to
bother. Please don't.
- No, no bother at
all. I'm finished.
Stay put right here.
I'll walk you home.
- [Crow] He asked
me, he asked me.
- Come on, let's go without him.
- No wait, maybe we
outta do what he says.
- [Mike] He is the janitor.
- You think he knows
about me and Jimmy?
Oh, what's the difference?
It's too late now.
Come on.
- [Tom Servo] They're going
to go neck in the alley.
- [Crow] Another busy Friday
night in downtown St. Paul.
- [Mike] Several hours later.
(Tom servo making
dramatic noises)
- [Crow] My diaphragm hurts.
- I'm beginning to wish
we'd waited for Mr. Wilson.
- It was your idea to leave.
- Well, we did.
- [Mike] Now we're
stuck in lake forest.
- Let's go this way.
- Okay.
- [Tom Servo] I live the
other way, but all right.
- [Crow] Angels,
hard as they come.
- [Mike] I can't stop.
- Come on Ann, we gotta go.
- Oh Betty, I can't.
- [Crow] I feel very
much for this pole.
- I've got to rest.
- [Tom Servo] Got to rest?
- Hey, did you hear something?
- [Mike] Sounds
like Ruth Underwood.
- No, I didn't hear anything.
- [Crow] I hate you.
- Look, I'm going. Come on.
- [Mike] Look, rhubarb.
(screaming)
- [Tom Servo] Oh,
I've had better dates.
- Ann.
- [Crow] Splendor in the
grass to dream warrior.
(screaming)
- [Tom Servo] Hey,
would you keep it down,
I'm trying to
strangle someone here.
- No!
- [Mike] Pepe Le
Pieu over there.
- [Crow] With action hips.
- [Mike] Now, is this a
teenager who strangled or
a person who's
strangles teenagers?
- [Tom Servo] Good question.
- [Crow] Let's watch on.
- [Tom Servo] Oh, anytime
VI does a production,
it turned out so well.
- [Crow] Oh yeah.
- [Tom Servo] Uses those
dirty canned onions and all.
- [Crow] American diversified.
It's produced by a food service.
(police siren blaring)
- [Tom Servo]
Geez, look at that.
Even dead, she looks great.
She can wear anything.
- [Mike] Oh I hate her.
- [Crow] I think
the dog did it, Ed.
- When did you find the body?
- We got a call about a half
an hour ago, Lieutenant.
And then, she was
there and I invested.
- [Tom Servo] I'm a guy.
- Looks like she got
it, just like the rest.
- Yes. Let's see.
It's the same MO.
- [Crow] He means
modus operendi.
- Around her neck.
Lipstick mark on her forehead.
- [Tom Servo] Yeah. He's a
humorous killer, ain't he?
- What kind of a nut would
do something like this?
- We're still trying
to find that out.
Three weeks ago was a 17
year old girl in Canola.
Last week. A student
teacher at the school.
Not much older than this kid.
- [Tom Servo] Let's review the
case in front of everybody.
- Can we take her
now, Lieutenant?
(laughing in the background)
- [Crow] It's not funny.
- Okay doc. You
can take off now.
- [Mike] Wait, let me gape
at her some more here.
- [Tom Servo] Ready?
(grunting noises)
- [Crow] Geez, she weighs a ton.
Move that keg out
of the way will ya.
There, thanks.
- [Tom Servo] Yeah.
Yeah. She'll fit.
I'll make her fit,
there always room.
- [Mike] Boy those ambulance
guy seem real nice.
- [Tom Servo] Pump it.
There we go.
- [Mike] Yeah. We always
talking about having lunch.
But just never get around to it.
- [Tom Servo] I
need a snicker bar.
- [Mike] Courtesy
boy on three, please.
- Lieutenant Anderson
to headquarters.
- [Crow] Anderson. That's me.
- We've finished here.
They've taken the
body to the morgue.
- [Crow] The guys
in the back seat.
- Wants to know if you've
got any more clues?
- No, nothing more than before.
- [Tom Servo] And don't rush me.
- Figure, it's the same one.
Tell Captain Murdoch.
I'll be in as soon as I
have finished around here.
Oh and you,
you better have a couple of the
boys down here to help Bill.
Are you 10 for?
- 10 for.
- Okay.
- [Crow] 10 for, that's
official cop talk, you know.
- Now, you'll have some help?
I want you to comb
this whole area.
Check out everything.
Streets, houses,
everything in the site.
Got some things to
attend to at the morgue.
- [Tom Servo] But
I'm the milkman.
Guess I could leave
him some yogurt.
- [Mike] All right,
I'll get to it tomorrow.
What could possibly happen
between now and then?
(police siren blaring)
- [Tom Servo] Who cares.
Six, 10.
I returned to the best Western.
- [Crow] Mindy Eisenhower.
- No youth. We don't
know who it was.
But it made no sense
until this morning.
- [Crow] Yes. I explained golf.
- We called the police.
- [Tom Servo] Yes.
He's dead. Dead. Dead.
- As a matter of fact, we're
expecting them at any moment.
- [Tom Servo] Six 11. They were
expecting us at any moment.
I ring the bell.
- The doorbell is ringing.
That must be them now.
I've got to hang up.
Yes.
- [Tom Servo] Okay
I'll join the ACLU.
- I'll call you later.
- [Mike] From community
theater to the big screen.
- [Crow] Now remember the three
S's, smiles, store, strong.
- Oh.
- I'm lieutenant Anderson.
Homicide division.
- [Tom Servo] Drop
the poodle and
step away from the condo please.
- Only one of you?
- [Mike] Arlo Wilson. Hmm.
- We've been expecting you.
They phoned you'd come.
Let's go into the living
room, my husband in there.
- [Crow] You're quite
handsome. Can I touch your gun?
- [Mike] Do we start
with stern questioning?
When do you become
physical with me?
- Dear? This is
Lieutenant Anderson.
- [Tom Servo]
Anderson, that's me.
- How do you do Lieutenant.
I knew a policemen once
back in my hometown.
- [Crow] Didn't like him.
- His name was Curtis Alston.
- The name I have is Anderson.
- [Tom Servo] That's me.
- I'm here on police business.
- Sit down won't you.
(farting noises)
- Terrible thing last night,
we could already understand.
(more farting noises)
- [Mike] It's the chair, sir.
- Mr. Royson, I'd like
to talk to your daughter.
- [Crow] Take a number pal.
- Had a rough time last night.
I don't think she's up yet.
- Listen. She's lucky
she can wake up.
Would you get Betty, please?
I'd like to ask
her some questions.
- Of course Lieutenant,
I'll get her right away.
- [Tom Servo] God, I would
trade places with you.
- DO you have any idea who
it might be Lieutenant?
How about some coffee?
- No, thank you.
I'll pass this time.
From what you informed
us last night,
your daughter didn't get
a positive identification.
- Well, that's what she said.
- What time did your
daughter get home last night?
- I really don't know for sure.
You see my wife and I
were out at the time.
- I see.
- [Crow] Enough said.
- Yes, we were at the
Frederick, a business meeting,
you know?
- Well, the first call
came in around 2:00 AM.
Is that right?
- Well, that's
when we came home.
I believe it was you
who called here later?
- Yes sir, that
was around 3:00 AM.
- Quite a night between calls.
I had to stay home
today from my business.
- [Tom Servo] I had diarrhea.
- To think a thing like this
could almost happen to your
daughter.
- It happened to someone's
daughter, Mr. Royson.
Someone's daughter who
was out with your daughter
until all hours of the night.
- Now see here, Lieutenant.
- [Crow] Stick it
where the sun don't-
- My daughter, she has
to be in by 10:00 PM.
We can't watch over her
like an old mother hen.
- [Tom Servo] Bock Bock.
- Picking on my
innocent little girl
who was almost killed
last night herself.
- Nobody's picking on
your daughter, Mr. Royson.
But you and every other
parent in town have known
about these attacks.
And it's your responsibility
to watch out after your kid.
- And your responsibility to,
you're getting paid
for it Lieutenant.
That's your job as a cop.
- And what's your
job as a parent?
- [Tom Servo] Are you
as turned on as I am?
(funky music)
- Oh, I do hope you
and the Lieutenant
are getting on real well.
- [Crow] Shut up.
- Betty will be down in
just a moment Lieutenant.
Can I get you a cup of
coffee or something?
- No thank you ma'am.
- [Crow] May I show you my slip?
- Dear, did you
tell him Michael's
we won't be over this evening?
This has been quite a shock
to both of us Lieutenant.
We really do feel as though
we should stay on with Betty
tonight.
That is right.
Isn't it Lieutenant?
- [Tom Servo] Easy now? Almost
there, they're only stairs.
- [Crow] Oh no, more stairs.
- Sit down here.
- [Crow] Pardon the
stain. I'm a cop.
(farting noises)
- I want you to tell
me everything you
can about last night.
- Yes, sir. I understand.
- [Crow] I kissed my
boyfriend and a girl died.
- It was so horrible.
I didn't know what-
- There there-
- Please Mrs. Royson,
let me handle this.
- Betty, I want you to
tell us everything you can,
in the first place.
Why did you come in so late?
- [Crow] Are you now, or have
you ever been a communist?
- I was with Jimmy last night.
- Jimmy?
How many times have I told you,
I don't want you running
around with that wild kid.
- Jimmy is not wild.
- Mr. Royson, let
me do the talking.
- Yes Lieutenant.
- [Mike] JAG off.
- [Tom Servo] What was that?
- Please, Mrs. Royson.
I'd like to talk to Betty.
- [Crow] Please clear the shot.
- [Mike] Looks like mom has
one, some dirt track trophies.
- Betty. Where were
you last night?
- [Crow] I waited
for you for hours.
- Jimmy and I
drove around a bit.
I planned to meet
Ann at the school.
We were going to tell our
folks that we'd been working at
the library.
- [Crow] This is hot. Hot.
- Ann and I met at the school
about 12:30-1:00 o'clock
- Betty, we're dealing with
a thrill killer, a madman.
If you, if you can
remember anything.
- [Mike] Punch it up a little.
Sell me this madman.
- Lieutenant.
- Yes?
- [Tom Servo] Yes.
Yes, Go on. More.
- It couldn't of
been one of the kids.
- [Crow] They're
all good Lutherans.
- It couldn't have. Could it?
- I don't know.
Whoever it is, is
familiar with the area.
Probably knows what
most of you do.
- It's just, oh, it couldn't
have been one of the kids.
- [Tom Servo] Okay, fine.
It couldn't have been
one of the kids. Geez.
- Well. The gang, the Fastbacks.
- The Hot Rodders. The
fast bunch he goes out.
- Yes, sir. What about them.
- I remember hearing Ann scream.
- [Crow] It went ahhh.
- I was walking
just a bit ahead.
- What then Betty?
- [Tom Servo] She was
looking at my butt.
- Has these white
emblems on their jackets.
And well, I,
I turned for just a
second and it looked like.
- [Mike] And you became a
pillar of salt. What, what?
- It couldn't of been one
of the kids Lieutenant,
it couldn't have, they
wouldn't hurt Ann like that.
- [Crow] Come on,
stop yodeling now.
- What is the emblem
you think you saw?
- But I'm not sure, it could've
been anything. I don't know.
- Betty. What do
you think you saw?
- A bulldog Lieutenant.
- [Tom Servo] Mcgruff?
- I might of seen a bulldog.
(funky music)
(men shouting orders)
(more yelling intangible orders)
- [Crow] Van Patton's
favorite hangout.
- Sorry, Tony.
No credit without we had a
chance to check your references.
- [Crow] Look, there's a
chef appearing tonight.
- It's rotten.
- Oh Shut up.
- Leave him aloe Mike.
- [Crow] The atmosphere here.
- Hey, Marty it's
okay. I'll pay for it.
- Okay.
- [Tom Servo] Ah, lunch
at the Russian tea room.
- The journey has to
raise tonight, Jim.
- I don't think so Curley.
- I kind of figured
you'd shut down.
You weren't there
last night either.
- I know, but.
- What?
- [Tom Servo] it's over Curley.
- You're going to drag it,
or you're going to drop it?
- Why don't you
just lay off Curley?
You know what
happened last night.
- [Tom Servo] Marty, What
do you wanna do tonight?
- Jerk. Betty almost
got killed too.
- For the very last
time runt, shut up.
- [Crow] Your finger
smells like bologna.
- Look Curley. Why
don't keep your back.
- [Tom Servo] Ooh.
- Hand off little man.
- You two break it up in here.
You got anything to settle.
- [Crow] Hey, Drew Carry.
- Settle it outside.
- [Crow] I breathe
a little easier
knowing the fry
cooks on the job.
- Hey gang, come on Jack.
- [Mike] Hey, it's Heidi.
- I'm sorry about last
night, Betty okay?
- I haven't seen her
yet, but I guess so.
She wasn't in any of
her classes today.
- [Crow] Good read, good.
- [Tom Servo] Hey you, dance.
- [Crow] This teen
joint brought to you
by the paneling council.
- Hey you ready Jack?
- [Mike] That was great.
- [Tom Servo] Hey,
get off my toast.
- Citizens! - [Crow, Mike
And Tom Servo] Union!
- Don't stand on the counter.
(shouting)
- Fellow citizens and
lovers of good music.
- [Tom Servo] You better leave.
- For those of you who pledge
your allegiance to Peter,
Paul and Mary.
(applause and cheering)
- [Tom Servo] They're dead. Woo.
- Those of you who have
undying love for the Beatles.
(cheering and applause)
- [Crow] Music grade T
musicians by Steven Right.
- [Mike] The dead Kennedy's.
- [Crow] Circle jerks.
- [Mike] The cramps.
- Not to mention the
Chad Mitchel trio.
(more cheering and applause)
- I finally introduce
you, to Mary and Jack,
The Huntington Astronauts.
(cheering and applause)
- [Mike] You can
see the ceiling,
Greg Toll must of
photographed this.
- Out of this world.
- [Tom Servo] That's
a joke. You see it.
- New sensation, just
released our new label.
- [Crow] You're standing
in my biscuits and gravy.
- Not a record mind you a label.
(laughing)
- [Crow] Check please.
- Ready?
- [Tom Servo] Hope these
kids have grief counseling.
- ♪I had a fella who told me♪
(Tom Servo making static noises)
♪I left the new
fashions and fold me♪
- [Crow] She's a peppy one.
♪ My sweety told me this is♪
(guitar music playing)
- [Mike] White flight.
- [All] White flight.
- [Mike] This is so...
- [Crow] Hey, is my
clown burger done?
(Mike making drum noises)
- [Crow] Thank you.
- [Tom Servo] Looks like the
dad from 'Family Circus'.
- [Mike] Hey, even Charles
Whitman at age nine,
got down with the polka music.
- [Mike] Like Charlie
Callous over there.
- [Crow] Give me
back my diaphragm.
- [Tom Servo] No.
- [Crow] Yes.
- [Mike] Boys must wash feet
before dancing on counter.
- [Crow] Patti
Smith nearly here.
- [Tom Servo] Oh, mama
told me not to come.
- [All] Zig Hail.
- [Crow] Let's see
your pantaloons again.
- [Mike And Tom Servo] Woo wee.
(loud cheering)
- [Crow] Thank you,
The Mickey's diners Audiences
are the greatest audiences
in the world. Woo.
- [Mike] Maria Callus, Thanks.
- [Tom Servo] Maybe
this was the start
of the counterculture.
(laughing)
- [Tom Servo] Love me.
- [Mike] I got a
tip at Oklahoma.
- [Tom Servo] Doing
the bug. Doing the bug.
- [Mike] Crazy kids. Look
at all these Yike Stripes.
- [Tom Servo] Oh no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Don't tap me. I'm
happily married.
- All right. Cut the noise.
Cut the jukebox.
- [Tom Servo] I want
to chick Sal sandwich
and I want to eat in peace.
- [Mike] Sir.
- Yes.
- [Tom Servo] Suck the
air out of the room.
(funky music)
(spitting noises)
- [Crow] Hey, this turf
is mine. Metal mouth.
(spitting noises)
- [Crow] Nothing doing Crow
mega nines rule the playground.
- [Tom Servo] Says who? Huh?
The Hover Mothers
own this blacktop.
We run this town.
- [Crow] Yeah.
We'll talk is cheap, chump.
You ready to rumble?
- [Tom Servo] I'm ready
to rumble. Let's go.
Oh wait, wait a minute.
I rolled in some gum.
- [Crow] Oh you got it? -
[Tom Servo] There I got it.
- [Crow] Oh okay.
- [Tom Servo] Okay
tough guy. Let's dance.
- [Crow] You and me,
going round and round.
- [Mike] Guys, guys, guys.
- [Tom Servo] What?
- [Mike] What's going
on? What are you doing?
- [Tom Servo] I'm about to
show this Cro-Magnon water boy
who's the boss around here.
- [Crow] You couldn't show
aunt Mabel the mall of America.
- [Tom Servo] Why you, I outta.
- [Mike] Guys.
I think the street gang
thing has gone far enough.
It's time we rapped.
- [Tom Servo] How's that?
- [Mike] You know, rap.
Lay it out in the
open, let's dialogue.
- [Crow] We were really
just playing Mike.
You know, it's make believe.
- [Tom Servo] Yeah.
No big thing, Mike. Okay.
- Guys. This street
is in my blood.
I grew up with this stuff.
Now what's going down.
- Mike, give us a break.
You grew up in little
chute, Wisconsin.
- Oh yeah.
We had streets and sometimes
they got pretty busy too.
On a Saturday night.
During crazy days.
When all the sidewalk
sales are going on,
it could seem just
like, hell town.
- Wow.
What you must've gone through.
Well, look at the
time I gotta get on.
- No, no nobody's leaving
till we figure out
what crime has been
perpetrated here.
- No crime. We
were just playing.
- Just playing. Huh?
Well, that's really funny Crow
because I knew another little
brother who was just
playing and you know what?
He bought himself a one-way
ticket to the bone orchard.
Now let me take a
guess here. Servo.
You dissed my little
brother Crow. Is that?
- Um dis as in disrespect?
- Yes.
- Sure. Always.
- Then you dissed me too.
- Well...
- When you cut my
compadre, you cut me,
and when you cut me, you
cut all men everywhere.
Am I getting through
to you guys on this?
- Oh, you made a
deep impression.
- Hey, Hey, Hey.Guys.
- Huh?
- Come on people now.
- No Mike that's-
- Smile on your
brother, everybody.
(alarm blaring)
- Saved by the movie sign.
(doors opening)
- Hey man don't tell
me we got another one.
- [Mike] Blessed the beast.
- [Crow] Shut your
cake hole Nelson.
- Anderson from homicide.
- [Tom Servo] Thank you,
Here. Thanks for
supporting live homicide.
- Most of you know what
happened last night.
Well we've reasoned to
believe that someone here
might be involved.
- [Crow] Someone bring
in my presentation.
- Hey Jimmy, what's going on?
- Just don't say anything.
Betty was not with me
last night. All right.
- Okay, but I-
- Young man.
- [Crow] Betty wasn't
with him last night.
- Me, sir?
- Yes. You've got
something to say.
I'd like to hear it.
- No, no, no sir.
- [Crow] Like,
sir, I smell bacon.
- You. - [Crow] Me?
- You. - [Tom Servo] Me?
- You and you. -
[Crow] Me and me.
- Come here.
Wait a minute.
- [Mike] Can I have this?
We need it for the cast.
- Who's jacket is this?
- what jacket?
- [Tom Servo] I got to
admit, that's pretty funny.
- All right now, somebody
here owns this jacket.
- That's mine officer.
Yeah. I hung it
there when I came in.
- [Tom Servo] You
can't wear black.
- What's your name?
- Tony.
- You're, you're sure
this is your jacket?
- Yes, sir. That's right.
- [Tom Servo] Now. You and
I have never met before.
Have we?
- How come the label,
says Jimmy Wall?
- Cause it's mine,
Lieutenant. It's my jacket.
He was just trying
to cover for me.
- [Mike] Trying to cover
up that I kill people.
He's a nut.
- All right. You five.
Let's take a ride
with me. Come on.
- [Crow] Ah geez.
Yikes stripes. What's the,
what the heck does that mean?
- [Tom Servo] It's visiting
day at the equipment room
at old high school.
- All right boys, get in there.
- [Mike] Excuse the mess, we
kind of live out of our jail.
- Where's the Sheriff?
- He's gone to the
television station,
broadcast the warning.
- Okay.
Tell him I let him know
if there's anything new.
- Yes, sir.
- [Crow] Say hi to
our TV audience.
- All right, hold it down
in here. Hold it down.
- [Tom Servo] Bored straits.
- Lieutenant.
- [Mike] Interrogation
room and showers.
- Let us go home.
- [Crow] These pants
are really tight.
- Listen, a girl was
murdered last night.
Another one scared
half outta her wits.
If you think this is a
comedy, you're crazy.
- [Tom Servo] Good.
This is funny.
- Your saying, you think
one of us had something to
do with all this?
- I'm not saying anything.
Now sit back and be quiet.
- [Crow] And don't
wear yellow anymore.
- I'll be right back.
- [Tom Servo] Okay.
Boys, cavity search time.
- [Crow] Geez. No more
killing all summer.
- Get off of it Curley.
- Hey look. We know none of
us had anything to do with it.
- Yeah, but where we drank
last night isn't sanctioned.
- Jude.
- [Crow] Jude? I specifically
heard him say Jude.
- So what? I know where
I was. You gonna tell him
where you were?
- Yeah Curley, we
could get arrested.
- Yeah man, were in a mess.
- I told him he
shouldn't have left.
- Cool it.
- [Mike] The man
wants us to fight.
- I got to think.
- [Tom Servo] Well,
you're all be hanged.
- Your parents have been called.
They're coming after you.
- Hey man, we're
getting paroled.
- Oh man, I'd rather stay
here then face the old man.
- [Crow] Why you I outta.
(making noises)
- Look, Lieutenant,
you still haven't told us
what this is all about.
- First, I want to know how
many more in your group?
- What do you mean, sir?
- I mean, this club you
belong to, these, jackets.
What do you call yourselves?
- The Fast Backs.
- [Tom Servo]
That's a dumb name.
- Number one,
group in the state.
- [Crow] We control shipping
from the inside out.
- The Fast Backs. Well,
how many are there?
- Just five man,
but where the best?
- [Tom Servo]
Quality since 1844.
- Best what?
- Drag, man. None can touch us.
(boys making car noises)
- All right!
- [Mike] Wow. I'm impressed.
- Are there any more
jackets like this?
- Well, lots of guys
at school wear em.
But not with a bulldog.
That's ours, strictly.
- Knock that off Curley.
(Crow making noises)
- It's just possible, one
of the you wearing these,
was seen last night.
- Seen where?
- You tell me where?
- [Tom Servo] It's a game.
- Beats facing my old man.
- What about you?
- [Mike] Surely not I lord.
- I wasn't with them.
- Where were you then?
- [Crow] I was in Austria
during the rumble.
- My, my dad thought
I was in my room,
but I slack out and met my girl.
- why were you supposed
to be in your room?
- My father found out
I joined the Fast Backs
and he grounded me.
- So he was joined this group?
- Yes sir. But I wasn't
with them last night.
I met my girl.
- But that still doesn't
account for your whereabouts
at the time of the murder.
- [Tom Servo] Sir. Do we
get attorneys or something?
- I met Betty at the school
then I went on at home.
- Your folks see you?
- No, sir.
I climbed back in
through the window.
I mean, they didn't even
know I was gone I guess.
- [Mike] I'm late,
what did I miss?
- I want you to
remind there parents,
we are releasing these
boys in their custody.
- Yes Sir.
- [Tom Servo] Eddie Egen.
- On your feet boys.
- I think I'd rather be
arrested and face my old man.
- All right, boys, follow me.
- [Mike] Time to introduce
you to your new husbands.
- Wait a minute, Jimmy.
Son.
- [Tom Servo]
You're real pretty.
- You got troubles.
Unless there's something
else you want to tell me?
- There's nothing
I can tell you.
- [Mike] Sometimes
I get all tingly.
- But I want your
promise. No sneaking out.
No seeing your girl.
And we'll let you go
home with your folks.
- [Crow] So I'm Gandi now?
- [Mike] Are cops,
constitutionally
able to ground kids?
- And now here's Cheryl
Frankel of Campbell county
with a special
message to parents.
(Crow and Tom Servo
exclaiming in shock)
- Parents and teenagers
of Campbell county.
- [All] Here.
- Last night,
a third child, was victim
of a dastardly crime.
Somewhere in this city,
a madman is preying
on teenage girls.
- [Crow] I believe it's me.
- Police department and
your Sheriff's office,
are doing their best to stop it.
We urge you not to try to take
the law into your own hands.
- [Mike] Cut it out guys.
- This as a civilized community,
all officers have been
directed to arrest
anyone found unlicensed,
arms or weapons.
We urge you, stay
home, stay safe..
- [Tom Servo] And cable up.
- You just heard a special
announcement brought to you as a
public service by channel 13,
we now returned to our
regularly scheduled programming.
- [Tom Servo] Untouchables,
busting up Frank Ninnies
speak easy in Cicero.
- [Tom Servo] Uh,
son, care to dance?
- Is that you Jon?
- Yes.
I've got Jimmy with me.
- Just a minute. I'm
turning the set off,
I'm coming right down.
- [Mike] I'm wearing
the French maid outfit.
- Dad.
- [Tom Servo] Overt your
eyes son, here comes mother.
- I just heard the Sheriff's
warning. It's terrible Jon.
- Yes.
- [Crow] Yeah. It
wasn't that bad.
- Our son is involved.
- [Tom Servo] Congratulations.
- Jimmy. You?
- Mom.
- Young man, you get
upstairs and you stay there.
- But dad-
- No but dad me. What
kind of a son have I got.
- You won't even
give me a chance.
(chuckling)
- You got a short memory.
- Hey mom.
- Mom, can I bring
some of the kids over?
Oh hi Jimmy, this afternoon
maybe we can do some-
- Mickey get upstairs.
- [Tom Servo] Your
brother is a killer.
- [Mike] I think we found Waldo.
- Get upstairs.
- [Crow] You know the rules.
How did you get unchained?
- All right.
- [Tom Servo] Anybody know him?
- Now the whole ugly
mess will come out again.
- [Mike] Hey, don't talk
about Mikey that way.
- I thought by
moving to Huntington,
that I'd spare
your mother and I,
the embarrassment
of the neighbors,
knowing that our
son was a thief.
But no, you had
to race hot rods.
Had to sneak out in the
middle of the night.
- John, maybe-
- Maybe nothing.
- Yes, dear. Thank you.
- Now you listen and
you listen straight.
You will stay in your
room from now on in.
I'll drive you to school.
I don't know what kind of a
mess this is going to turn out
to be.
I don't know what
we're going to do.
- [Tom Servo] Curse
of the starving class.
- By Jupiter, you'll stay
in your room this time.
- [Mike] Oh, don't
invoke Jupiter name.
Your mother will come and
pick you up and then into your
room.
- [Crow] Now give me a hug.
- Now.
Now get upstairs.
And you stay there.
- [Tom Servo] Okay.
- [Mike] Is this love?
- And leave Mickey alone.
- [Crow] He's
working on his novel.
- [Mike] I love it when you
act like Dur Fuhrer honey,
let's commit the marriage act.
- Jon.
- Marsha.
- What are we going to do?
- I don't know.
- [Tom Servo] Let's
learn Italian.
I've always wanted
to learn Italian.
- I Just don't know June.
(knocking on door)
- What?
- It's me Jimmy.
- [Tom Servo] Can I have
best dress in albums back?
- Can I come in?
- No.
- Please.
- [Mike] I want to
make you feel better.
- Dad said no.
- [Crow] But I've got
my TJ Fridays outfit on.
- Mom's next door.
- [Tom Servo] With
her head in the oven.
- Please let me come
talk to you, Jimmy.
- [Mike] Will you
give me a swirly?
- Please?
- All right.
But stop you're sniffling.
- [Crow] The Amish
kids beat me up again.
- What are you going to do?
- Rotten in this room, I guess.
I don't know.
- Jimmy.
- [Tom Servo] Am I blooming?
- I'm sorry.
- It's not your fault.
- But Dad so upset.
- Yeah,
I guess I can't blame him much.
- But it's all my fault.
- [Mike] Well, only in the
sense of original sand.
- We said we'd
never talk about it.
- But I gotta
Jimmy. I just gotta.
It's my fault you're
in this mess now.
- Your fault?
You didn't sneak out last night.
- But you didn't
steal that bike.
- No and you didn't either.
- [Crow] Oh Jimmy.
- I should have told him then.
I only borrowed it because,
because you wouldn't
let me use yours.
I didn't steal it. Honest.
- I know you didn't.
- But you didn't neither.
- Why didn't you just tell them?
- Look, we promised, it's over.
- [Tom Servo] Push
Jimmy push. Come on.
- Let me tell the folks please?
- No. (all of them
yell in surprise)
- You think it will
make any difference now?
I'll be all right.
- [Mike] Oh God. He's a 10.
(Tom servo and Crow yelling)
- Just leave it be. Leave me be.
Get out of here.
- [Tom Servo]
Mickey's down, medic!
- Hey, I'm sorry.
Hey, come on, Mikey.
(Mickey crying)
- [Tom Servo] ♪So I
sing you to sleep♪
♪After the love♪
- Look, do you really
want to do me a favor?
- Yes.
- [Mike] Here, put
this ointment on.
- Will you take this
note to Betty for me?
Don't let anyone see
you give it to her.
- Okay.
- [Crow] It's a
prescription for Valium.
- You just deliver this.
- [Crow] Okay.
- I'll take it to her right now.
- Hey, tell her uh.
- [Tom Servo] You're
really not my brother.
- Tell her I hope she's okay.
- All right.
- [Mike] And stay away
from the riverfront.
And no more pretending
you're Lord Byron.
- [Tom Servo] Whoa.
- [Crow] Hey, it's wet here.
- [Tom Servo] Jimmy,
uh, girlfriend,
- [Crow] Clang, clang,
clang went the trolley.
- [Crow] Pansy Graham.
- [Tom Servo] Mr. I'm
here for my beating.
- [Mike] Okay, okay
is home Betty, no.
Oh, is available, but Betty,
oh I dunno what the, Ah.
- Is Betty home Mrs. Royson?
It's important honest,
I gotta talk to her.
- Well, I'll see. You wait here.
- [Crow] Your safe I guess.
- [Tom Servo] If I could
just smell a few cushions,
I'd be happy.
- [Mike] Don't flip the
furniture this time.
- Betty?
Betty?
- Yes, mother.
- There's a young
man to see you.
I'll be right down.
- You're in.
She'll be right down.
Wait here, young man.
- [Crow] You little freak.
- [Mike] I could
really confide in her.
- [Tom Servo] Will you
make me some lunch, uh oh.
- Who is it?
Oh.
- [Tom Servo] What are you?
- What do you want?
- I'm sorry about what
happened, Betty, but,
but Jimmy didn't do it.
- Jimmy didn't do what?
Who said he did?
- Police. They're
saying he did it.
He gave me this for you.
- He was with me.
I told them that.
- [Crow] Oh it's moist.
- [Tom Servo] Please knee
this kid in the groin.
- Mikey, tell him I'll
sneak out tonight.
Tell him, I'll meet
him at Marty's.
- Okay, but he's not
supposed to go out.
- I'm not supposed
to see him either,
just tell him I'll be there.
- Okay, but.
- [Mike] But what about the
boom shadow that just crossed
behind us?
- I'll tell him
Betty, I'll tell him.
- [Tom Servo] Geez,
what is that smell?
- [Crow] Well, that
went well I thought.
I reached out to another
human being and was not
slapped down.
- [Tom Servo] Ha, I can chew
and dance at the same time.
Hehe.
- [Mike] I said, let's go
outside so I could strangle you.
- [Crow] Eddie or Carolyn
and a net full of cello,
out on the town.
- Hi Tony, Elaine.
- Hi.
- Hi Betty. How you feeling?
- Oh okay I guess.
- [Crow] My neck hurts
from the strangler.
- Gee that's a nice song.
- [Mike] It's the only song.
- He wants to get
the place some class.
- [Tom Servo] Or shut up.
You're no, Jerry Paris.
- Hey um, can I
get you something?
- Oh no, I don't think so.
- How about a sip of my pop?
I mean, there's nothing in it.
Am I the only drink that
can make that statement?
(laughing)
- [Crow] I didn't get it.
- Betty can we get you anything?
- Oh no, thank you, Marty.
- Eddie, how you doing kid?
- [Mike] Oh, my tennis arm.
- Uh oh, here comes trouble.
- [Tom Servo] Trent Trouble.
- Well hi Betty, how about
wrestling this one with me?
- No, I don't think so.
- [Crow] That would be strange.
- Why? I'll help you
shake your blues.
- The lady says no.
- You've got a real
bad memory runt.
- [Crow] And your no
good at languages.
- Oh, come on.
- [Mike] Someone shut that music
off. It's driving me crazy.
- I'm going to have to
play teacher and learn you
a lesson you'll never forget it.
You open your mouth
just one more time.
Now you sit back.
- [Tom Servo] Yipe Stripes.
Get the crap kicked outta your-
- Why don't you leave her
alone, you know she's Jimmy's
girl.
- Yeah. Well Jimmy's
been grounded see.
He's all cooped up. This
little bird can still fly.
- [Crow] Take it back.
- [Crow] Oh, you
hurt my pant area.
- Give me room.
- [Tom Servo] Give
him a banana split.
- [Mike] Get the burger.
- I'm gonna mop your
floors, the head mop.
- You'll have to
start with me Curley.
You think you're big enough.
- [Mike] You're not
impacting anymore.
- I was only kidding.
- You and your buddies
get out of here and don't
come back, your hear?
- The service stinks anyways.
- Curley.
You owe me 30 cents
for three drinks.
- Bill me.
- Where? In the hospital?
30 cents cash. No credit.
- [Tom Servo] If
that's okay with you?
- [Crow] Randy Quad,
ladies and gentlemen.
- You and me still
got a mopping date.
- [Crow] Okay. How's Tuesday?
- Out.
- [Tom Servo] How's
that? Just keep oh, okay.
- [Mike] Well, I was
really gonna get him
if he hadn't slammed
me against the wall,
that really broke my momentum.
- [Crow] Gary, I broke
up with you while
you were over there
getting trashed.
- [Tom Servo] The hell.
- [Mike] Peter
Weller's back in town.
- Hi Jimmy.
- Sit down, Jimmy. I'll
see your kids later.
- What happened to you?
- Oh nothing.
- Curley, he got
fresh with Betty.
- Oh, it was nothing,
Marty threw him out.
- [Tom Servo] Slammed
against the wall again. Huh?
- Look, do you two mind?
- Know. Sure. We, we
know three's a crowd,
four is a jam.
- [Tom Servo] Ha. He's
still got a sense of humor.
- [Mike] Okay, I got the stuff.
- He's really a nice guy.
- [Crow] I can be a nice guy.
- So are you Jimmy.
Oh, what are we going to do?
- Nothing.
- [Tom Servo] Just like
what we've been doing
the whole movie.
- I mean, I've got
to leave Huntington.
- But why? You
didn't do anything.
- I know but they think I did.
I've got my stuff packed.
- Where are you going?
- I don't know. I'll
get a job somewhere.
I'll write you.
- Jimmy. Please.
- [Mike] Come to terms
with their sexuality.
- If my folks found out,
that I was with you tonight,
I'd never get out again,
but I just had to see you.
- For me too. I just
had to tell you that.
- Tell me what?
- [Crow] You make me feel funny.
- I know things are a mess now,
but someday they'll
straighten out.
I'll come back. I mean,
will you wait for me?
- Oh, you know, I will,
but running away,
isn't going to help.
- What am I going to do?
- Jimmy?
- [Mike] Have the Texas toast.
- If you love me. I
don't know what I do.
- Me too, honey.
I got in trouble once
before. It wasn't my fault.
But, now it looks like,
they blame me for these things.
- [Crow] And the
Hindenburg disaster.
- You know it wasn't
me you saw that night?
- No. I just saw the jacket.
Oh, I don't know what I saw.
- [Tom Servo] You two
gonna order or what?
- Let me take you home.
I gotta think, maybe
is I walk or something.
- [All] ♪ God Bless America. ♪
Land♪
(funky music)
- [Mike] Some people
might not realize,
that it was basically
an offensive maneuver
to let him slam
me into the wall.
Oh, that's not your house.
I'm a little disoriented
after the fight.
- [Crow] So, do you
got a water bed?
- [Tom Servo] Oh,
that's really safe.
- [Mike] That's the
first place they look.
- I thought you said
your folks would be home.
- Well, it's a little
earlier than I thought.
Don't worry, I'll be all right.
You want me to walk you home?
- No.
- [Mike] Well maybe.
- You uh, you want
me to come in?
- Nuh uh.
- [Tom Servo] You can flip
any chick in the house,
Why me?
- Goodnight, Tony.
- [Mike] It was the slam against
the wall thing. Wasn't it?
- [Crow] Oh, by the way,
we're just friends, okay, bye.
- [Mike] Well, Home
at, ait a minute.
He dropped me off
at the wrong house.
- [Tom Servo] Goodnight, Tony.
- [Mike] Well, my ride's
here anyway. I couldn't kiss.
- [Crow] Nah, she won't
be strangled tonight.
- [Tom Servo] Hmm,
Tumblr is for the yellows
and I'll be set for the night.
- [Crow] Mom. No. Get back in
there. What have we told you?
(humming the tune)
- [Mike] God I hate that song.
- [Crow] I like it.
(making noises to the tune)
- [Tom Servo] Let's
see if king baskets on.
- [Crow] She's turned on the
all Yikes Stripe station.
- [Mike] Ooh.
- [Tom Servo] That lady
really doing the trick.
(fun radio music)
(making drum noises)
- [Tom Servo] It's Gypsy
Rose Lee in the venture
teaming up for the
naughtiest teen scene every.
- [Tom Servo] Well, she sure
that's plaid look tasty,
doesn't she.
- [Mike] She gets pretty
good sound from that radio.
- [Crow] This is when
strangling was more convenient.
Strangler came
right to your house.
- [Mike] In 30 minutes.
- [Tom Servo] Watchtower.
- [Mike] Oh, its the
Naughty Jack tripper again.
- [Crow] Nice set a calves, huh?
- [Tom Servo] Oh boy, oh mama.
- [Crow] Well, I certainly
hope there's some application
or some non-skid surface in
that tub for safety sake.
- [Tom Servo] Oh, let me guess.
(whistling killer tune)
- [Mike] I'll just
change it to classical.
I can't work with
this rock music.
- Hey mom, is that you?
- [Tom Servo] Yes it is.
- [Crow] Abraham Lincoln?
- [Tom Servo] Oh, it's
Andrew Dice. Clay of course.
- [Mike] Jack and
Jill went up the.
- Mother?
Mother?
(screaming)
- [Mike] It's my
turn for the shower.
- [Crow] You're not fully dead
until you're zestfully dead.
- What the? convertible
cop car with a siren.
(police siren blaring)
- [Mike] Ah, damn
solar eclipses.
(all making noises)
- Down the street
visiting neighbors.
- Is Jimmy in his room?
- Yes. Jimmy's upstairs.
He's confined to his room.
- Well would you, would
you get him please?
- [Crow] I'm Michael Anthony.
- I'm a neighbor of
theirs, what's the trouble?
- There's been another murder.
- Oh No.
- [Crow] It wasn't me
who was murdered, was it?
- [Tom Servo] Meanwhile,
Teen boys steps into action.
Teen-Mobile away.
- [Mike] Teen Boy is
filmed in blue vision.
- [Crow] Well, he looks
like a probable suspect.
I'm going to apprehend him.
(police siren blaring)
- [Crow] More people should
use their turn signals.
- [Mike] A daring chase scene,
well within the
confines of the law.
- [Crow] Damn you, Duke boys!
- [Tom Servo] Maybe I should
take down his license plate
number and call it
in or something.
- [Crow] See the incredible
school zone action.
- [Tom Servo] Okay.
Come on, come on.
- [Mike] So they stopped at
Henry David Thoreau's cottage.
- [Tom Servo] Teen boy,
there's trouble on the
other side of town.
(Crow giggling)
- [Mike] Been working
out? You feel pretty good.
- Get the keys.
- [Crow] Could you
frisk me again please?
- I'm sorry, Lieutenant.
I got scared.
- Son, you scared a lot of us.
Come on. Let's go.
This time, I'll drive.
- [Tom Servo] Scaring all
of us is a felony son.
- [Mike] Can I sit in the front?
Makes me feel like you're
my chauffeur or something.
- [Crow] Airport.
Make it snappy.
Just kidding, sir.
(police siren blaring)
- [Tom Servo] He has a
really gritty street feeling
to it doesn't it?
- [Crow] You want to stop
for some me xix skins?
- [Tom Servo] Later
at Cal Berkeley.
- [Mike] Free Huey.
- [Crow] Off the pigs. Hehe.
- [Mike] Come here,
you a little prodigy.
I'll give you your Mensa.
- [Crow] Oh look that janitor
is into the grunge look.
- What do you think about
what happened last night.
- [Tom Servo] I think it's good.
- I think it's terrible.
You kids outta
have better sense.
- [Tom Servo] Now go
about your business.
- You really clean
up on your job.
- Jimmy didn't do
anything. I know it.
- Sure. Just wanted
to go for a joy ride.
Kids nowadays.
- [Tom Servo] Hula hoops
and ice cream sodas.
Kids is all,
just kids.
- [Crow] What an
insightful janitor. Huh?
- [Crow] Angels.
I want you to go undercover
as tennis players.
- [Mike] Wow. That was
good pot. Wasn't it.
- Hi Mickey, what
are you doing here?
- Betty I gotta talk to ya.
- Sure.
- I just gotta.
- [Tom Servo] I think
I'm a hermaphrodite.
- You gotta help him. Gotta.
- Who, what are
you talking about?
- You mean you don't
know about Jimmy?
- What about Jimmy?
- [Crow] He's my brother.
- He got arrested last
night. Cause he wasn't home.
Another girl got killed
and he wasn't home.
So they arrested him.
- I know he went
home. He promised me.
- I know, but, but the
police came just as he,
well, he got scared and
drove off and dad's car.
- [Mike] Don't hit me.
- When they caught him.
He said he couldn't tell where
he was. He just couldn't.
- Oh my gosh. He was with me.
- I know, but he
won't tell them.
- Oh, it's all my fault.
I told him I'd get into trouble.
- Betty, what are
we going to do?
We can't let him get blamed.
What are we going to do?
- [Crow] Rub your face
and crunchy underwear.
Well I'm sorry.
- Come on.
- [Mike] I need some chocolate.
- [Tom Servo] Oh Betty.
I could be beat up
in so many ways here.
- [Crow] Hey, weren't we going
to beat the crap out of him.
- [Mike] It's a next
time, It's implied.
- Yes, Captain.
Yeah, we caught him,
but he won't say anything and
just that he didn't do it.
And he won't tell
us where he was.
- [Mike] Yes, we
gave him a swirly.
- He says he ran out
because he was scared.
And Captain, you know something.
- [Crow] You're fired.
- I kinda believe him.
I don't know why, but,
but something's wrong.
- [Tom Servo] So what's the
other important information
you wanted to
tell- Hello, hello.
- Lieutenant, there's a couple
of kids out here to see you.
- [Tom Servo] They're
waiting in my neck flap.
- [Mike] An unlikely couple.
- Betty, son, come on in.
Come on Betty.
- [Tom Servo] We're
very upset about
the school lunch program.
- Lieutenant Anderson.
- [Crow] That's me.
- He didn't do it.
He didn't do it,
he was with me last night.
The reason he didn't
tell you was cause he
knew I'd get into trouble.
If my folks found out
that I sneaked out, but he
didn't do it Lieutenant,
he was with me.
- And he didn't
steal no bike either.
- [Tom Servo] What?
- I did,
he just wanted...
- [Tom Servo] Good
lord. Who is this clown?
- Just calm down.
Get control of
yourself. Sargent.
- [Tom Servo] Get
them outta here.
- [Crow] Hose these two off.
- [Tom Servo] Beautiful
scene, just riveting.
(door closing)
(laughing)
- So here's the plan.
- Okay.
- Mike walks into the room.
- Plausible.
- Put's on those glasses.
And thanks to a tiny electrode
that scrambles his left brain
function. He becomes,
goofy, doofy, wimpy,
Mikey from the movie.
(laughing)
- God, I love technology.
- Oh Mama.
Let me tell you-
- Oh shh, here he comes.
- Hi guys. Hey, you
mind if I join you?
- Oh. Hey, no problem Mike,
always room for the
big blonde human.
- That's me.
- Yup.
- In fact, uh, Mike.
We were wondering if you'd
looked something up in the there
dictionary for us.
- Right there. This
dictionary there.
- Sure, that print is small.
- Well you could
use those glasses,
- Right there,
- All right.
Hey what's with the cord?
- Um, they're digital.
Yeah. Digital
(laughing)
- Well, What did you
want me to look up?
- Um, how about rhyme.
- Rhyme?
- Yeah.
R I M E.
- It's a homonym for
the other word, rhyme?
- I'm sorry, Jimmy.
Mom's so upset.
Jimmy you gotta come back Jimmy.
So rhyme. Does that help?
- Mike, you didn't finish.
- Yeah.
- I didn't?
(more laughing)
- Rime,
an accumulation of oh, granular.
And I didn't steal
no bike neither.
It was all me I did it, it
was my fault please Betty.
- Wow. So that's rime,
which is a hominine for
the other word rhyme.
- You know, I think you would
look good in black glasses.
- No no no.
- Yeah, you'd loo good.
Hey, let's go clean
your head Servo.
- [Tom Servo] I don't need it.
- Okay. I can hold it together.
Jimmy.
No,
I me.
The sheriff wanted to
see you right now Jimmy.
I'd take that letter to Jimmy.
No, I'm sorry, Jimmy.
I didn't ask for no
commercial sign neither.
(Crow rambling)
(funky music)
- [Tom Servo] Oh,
Incredible, sexless girl-man
tells all in crying JAG.
Woo, I'm a teenage
strangling, man.
- [Crow] You have to
take the glasses off.
- [Mike] What are you doing?
Oh. I'm sorry.
Don't want you to
be Micky all day.
- [Crow] Thank you.
- Well, if it ain't
the little hero.
- [Tom Servo]
Jonathan Silverman.
- They never would of caught me.
- Maybe it's better this way.
- The offer still goes, baby.
want to drop slow poke here.
My chariot is gassed and ready.
- [Crow] English. Please.
- Why don't you just hop in
and get on outta here then.
And take this with you.
- [Mike] And thus, the
haberdasher turf war began.
- [Crow] Is this a good
time to mention there's a
strangler loose.
- [Crow] Boeing, Haha.
- [Mike] Yeah, they're
tough aren't they.
The goofiest fight.
(Tom Servo singing)
- [Mike] I am not a crook.
- [Crow] Just another day on the
'Beverly Hills 9 0 2 1 0' set.
- [Mike] This is what
happen when you serve
tuna wiggle for lunch.
- Break it up!
Or I'll report you
to the principal.
- [Tom Servo] Sprinkle
saw dust on all of you.
(laughing)
- Man I'll take you
on any other way too.
- Well I get my kick some
speed if you got the nerve.
- I got it.
- [Mike] Looks like
operations rescue.
- Pull up.
- I'll out run you
just like before.
- Tomorrow.
- [Tom Servo] I
love ya, tomorrow.
- [Mike] Oh, that
was too easy, Tom.
- [Crow] I agree,
Wish I'd said it.
- [Mike] Now Hugs
all around. Come on.
- [Tom Servo] By the way.
Can I borrow your econ notes?
- You promise.
- Yeah, maybe you outta
listen to mama Jimmy.
- Tomorrow at the strip.
- Come one.
- [Mike] What's his bread
album to do with it?
- [Crow] I don't know.
- [Tom Servo] Look, Katie
Lang is in their group.
- [Mike] Next time.
We'll debate him right?
- I don't like this Jimmy.
- Jimmy why do you
have to prove yourself?
- [Crow] Because I'm short.
- I gotta Betty.
I guess I asked for it.
I can't back down now.
- Hey let's go to Marty's,
I'll buy you a pop.
- [Tom Servo] Pop, that's
your answer to everything.
- Hey Jimmy.
- [Mike] Yes, Tony.
- Hey don't you
want your jacket?
- Nope. Not anymore.
- [Crow] It's mid July.
- [Mike] Well, here
you go, director.
- [Tom Servo] You're
fun to study with Gary.
- [Crow] Next time,
on sweating bullets.
- [Mike] Crime time
after prime time.
- [Mike] New orchestra.
- [Crow] Excuse me. Could
I have a word with you?
- [Tom Servo] Oh Henry, please.
Not every time I come home.
- [Crow] Serial killing is easy.
Once you get the hang of
it. I'm Marshall Brody.
- [Tom Servo] They
killed Vivian Vans.
- [Mike] Every man's mom. Dead.
(car engines revving)
- [Crow] They're behind
you. I have that problem.
- [Tom Servo]
Suddenly it's dadio.
- [Crow] I'm trying to get the
Danny Thomas
silhouette just right.
- [Tom Servo] Come on, come on.
Sit, sit, stay, stay,
sit, come on, come on.
Sit, stay, stay.
- I'll meet you at the
other end. If you make it.
- We'll see.
- [Mike] How's
that make you feel?
- Let's get started.
- [Crow] Hunter Thomson.
- [All] Whoopie! Hoo hoo.
(car screeching)
- [Tom Servo] 25 miles
an hour to death.
- [Crow] They like to look at
the scenery as the drag race.
- [Mike] Real pretty.
- [Crow] Oh yeah.
- [Mike] Jimmy pops the clutch
and politely asked the world,
which mind eating
my dust so much?
- [Tom Servo] As a matter
of fact, I do own the road.
- [Crow] Hey you who,
your blinkers on.
- [Mike] In a few years,
this whole area all built up.
- [Tom Servo] Oh it's a shame.
Hey, what say about a picnic?
- [Crow] Corn job. Haha.
- [Tom Servo] I
see, I see, I see.
- Jimmy.
Jimmy stop. I gotta talk to you.
- [Mike] I haven't
sold enough grit.
- [Crow] Look out
that's razer wire.
- [Tom Servo] I think I'm
barren now or something.
- Mikey, are you okay?
I'm sorry. I didn't hear you.
- [Mike] Is your hair on okay?
- [Tom Servo] I'll
beat myself up.
- I'm all right.
Ma, he hardly missed me,
mom says to call
Lieutenant Anderson. Right away.
It's important Jimmy.
- [Tom Servo] You got to go home
and empty the dishwasher Jimmy.
- Stay with him.
- Sure.
- I'll get to you later Curley.
- [Tom Servo] Okay.
- Stay with him honey.
- [Mike] Come on, there's a
sale at Laura Ashley, come on.
- [Crow] A phone, what
a convenient drag race.
- [Tom Servo] The call
is coming from, me.
- I like the police
department, please.
- [Mike] Any police
department will do.
- Yes, this is Jimmy Walton.
Could I speak with
Lieutenant Anderson, please?
Thank you.
- [Mike] Why does
Jimmy Walton call.
- [Crow] The FBI didn't
have many files back then.
Yello.
- Lieutenant Anderson.
- Hello, Lieutenant.
This is Jimmy.
- [Mike] Oh hi.
- Yes Jimmy. Now
listen carefully.
I want you to get to the
rest of the Fast Backs
and have them come to
my office on the double.
Nevermind.
We found one of your emblems
and I want all of you in my
office immediately.
That's right.
- [Crow] His office is
in the boy's bathroom.
- [Tom Servo] So who wants
to drag race guys, guys?
- Hey Jack, see if you can
get the guys back here.
- [Tom Servo] Us?
- [Mike] Me?
- [Crow] And action.
- [Mike] Anyway, it's
my pride that got hurt.
At least my shirts okay.
- Quitting already.
- Look, we're all going down
to Lieutenant
Anderson right now.
- [Tom Servo] It'll be fun.
- I told him we'd all be there.
- Yeah, well you don't
promise no cop nothing.
- Don't be a fool.
They found something.
Jane Houston, was
strangled last night.
- [Crow] She was
strangled last week.
- Hey Curley
where's your emblem?
- [Mike] Um, my
mom's washing it.
- It's in my locker. Why?
- Cause that's what they
found near Jane Houston.
- [Tom Servo] Oh.
- It's in my locker. It
came off this morning.
Now look, no one's
gonna pin this on me.
- You're going with us
to Lieutenant Anderson.
- [Crow] I think I hear
my mom calling, Oh.
(screaming and shouting)
- [Mike] Oh, an able-bodied
assist from Mikey.
- [Crow] Michael. I
shut the door for you.
- [Tom Servo] Bye-bye now.
- [Crow] Bye.
- [Mike] Bye-bye.
- [Crow] Nice kids eh?
(cars screeching)
- [Tom Servo] No, don't
you dare go through that.
Don't you go to that yard.
- [Mike] The battle
of the network sedans.
- [Crow] Junior car rodeo
with old timer Billy Sladder.
- [Mike] You can't squealing
in dirt. It's impossible.
- [Tom Servo] Maybe,
Helen Mede was
brought in to this scene.
(car screeching)
- [Crow] Stop that.
- [Tom Servo] Really.
- [Mike] Big pass
on the rodeo clowns.
- [Tom Servo] Driving at speeds
approaching the
actual speed limit.
- [Mike] Mikey, would
you please move over?
The other way, Mikey.
- [Crow] Well, at least
it's a nice day for it.
- [Tom Servo] What the?
- [Mike] How could
it be on that side?
- [Tom Servo] Now the
camera man fell over.
- [Crow] Haha. He crashed,
then shot himself.
(laughing)
(shouting out Curley's name)
(funky music)
- [Tom Servo] You could
learn a lot from a dummy.
- [Mike] Do they have
to play the horse silver
for his accident?
- [Crow] I get his jacket.
- [Mike] You know what we have
to do. We gotta pants him.
(Curley mumbling)
- It's in my locker.
- [Tom Servo] Looks like they're
in Vietnam all of a sudden.
- Maybe it is.
Gosh, what have we done?
- It couldn't be, Betty,
checked his locker.
- Okay.
- Tony, call
Lieutenant Anderson.
- Yeah right.
- [Tom Servo] Uh, Curley
we'll be with you shortly.
Please stand by.
- [Mike] I'm taking your
car. I have your checkbook
- [Crow] And put
some gas in it too.
Won't go backwards all the way.
Oh No. Mr. Be naturals
in one of those lockers.
- [Mike] Oh. Friend is dying.
- [Crow] You have a
very small student body.
- [Tom Servo] Trying to make
it real compared to what.
- Mr. Wilson, you frightened me.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh, I'm trying
to find something
or not find it or something.
- What are you mumbling about?
- I have to check
Curley's locker,
he said he left
something in there.
Oh, Mr. Wilson, it's terrible.
- Well, now we'd
better open the locker.
Have a master key.
- [Mike] We call it a master
key. Cause it opens every door.
One of your basic janitor tools.
It's actually quite a bit
of responsibility. Hehe.
- [Tom Servo] You've
been eating Spaghetti Os.
- Oh my gosh.
- What is it?
- [Crow] My art project.
- The emblem. It
wasn't his locker.
- Child, I don't have a notion
of what you're talking about.
- I found the emblem.
Oh, Jimmy might've killed him.
Oh Mr. Wilson.
- Now child, just calm down.
Come on, go into my
office for a minute,
will fix you a cup of tea.
- Oh, what are we going to do?
- Just calm down.
(Mike does a goofy evil laugh)
- [Crow] Why don't I just
strangle myself then.
- [Mike] I actually prefer
the term custodian, after all
I like to think of myself as
a concierge for the students.
Oh, here's where I stare at
the cheerleaders right in here.
- Now, you sit.
- [Mike] I'll strangle.
- While I'm fixing us
some tea, you tell me
what it was you found.
- [Crow] Do you have camomile.
- Who got hurt?
- Jimmy. Oh I mean Curley.
You see the emblem on his jacket
was missing and they found
one by Jane Houston. And
we thought, but he didn't,
he didn't do it.
I know he didn't
do it. Mr. Wilson.
- [Tom Servo] Oh I'm
babbling, I know I, what the?
- Mr. Wilson.
- [Mike] You know
you can't wear pink.
- [Crow] Oh, he Uh, ran
with Malcolm Forbes.
- [Tom Servo] Oh cool.
- This is, this is Jimmy's.
But,
But Tony threw it away.
- [Mike] Lady. It's time
to get on the clue bus.
- I,
found the jacket,
the emblem was already off.
- [Tom Servo] Oh, okay.
So how about that tea?
- But when he threw
it away, it wasn't.
- [Crow] Get back to us when
you have a whole
sentence worked out.
- Mr. Wilson, I want
to go home, please.
- No.
- [Mike] The master wants
you but he can't have you.
- You don't want to
go home just yet.
- [Tom Servo] Need
more sugar in our tea.
- Please, Mr. Wilson.
- Oh, your saying
please Mr. Wilson.
Yes all of a sudden
it please Mr. Wilson.
Your bunch doesn't
usually say please.
- [Tom Servo] On
this manners murder.
- Mr. Wilson won't please.
- But why? Why?
- Why?
For the student just
like you, years ago.
She said.
- [Mike] Oh something
or other, I don't know.
- I used to be a teacher then.
- [Crow] Then I
rolled the lawnmower.
- She said I tried to touch her.
- [Tom Servo] Like this?
- I wasn't even there, but the
school board wouldn't listen.
Now look where I am.
Mr. Wilson the janitor.
You think I like it?
- [Tom Servo] Yes. No.
- I like cleaning up after a
bunch of grubby kids like you?
I hate it.
- [Crow] You have
lovely the eyes though.
- [Mike] Should see
a guidance counselor.
- But the jacket I
saw the first time.
- [Tom Servo] I'm glad
you asked that question.
- This one,
I forgot about the paint smear.
- [Crow] I tried
scrubbing it out.
- In the dark, it might
of looked like a bulldog.
- [Tom Servo] Or a park bench.
- And it gave me the idea.
They might've thought it was
one of you, but no, you had to.
(screaming)
- [Mike] Fortunately the
Higgins boys and Grubber
were on the scene.
- [Tom Servo] Pete, Link, Tony.
- [Crow] Hey, look what
the janitor is doing.
- [Mike] Hey.
(yelling)
- [Mike] Cattle is...
- [Crow] Need control top.
(screaming)
- [Tom Servo] Ah, what the hell,
I'll just shoot in
here from times.
- [Mike] What happened.
- [Crow] Well he's union. So
they won't be able to fire him.
(gun shots fired)
- [Crow] The Lysols, in the...
- [Tom Servo] Punch
me out, please.
- [Tom Servo] Can
you believe it?
Strangled with sandal toes.
- [Mike] Ironically. There's
no one there to clean him up.
- He did it,
he was crazy.
He killed all those girls.
- It's okay honey, it's over.
It's all over now.
- [Tom Servo]
Congratulations. It's over.
Tell her what she's won Johnny.
- You boys had a good
sense of the call.
- [Crow] By the way,
what were you doing
in that scene?
- [Tom Servo]
Well, that was fun.
(groaning)
- [Crow] It's an epilogue.
- Out of the hospital today.
- Yeah.
- It's our fault, isn't it?
- I don't know
what to say to him.
- Hey, look,
Lieutenant Anderson.
- [Mike] And he's wearing pants.
- Got a friend of yours with me.
- [Tom Servo] What?
- Marty, is it all right?
- [Tom Servo] Okay!
- Sure, Bring him in.
- [Mike] Maybe it's Jesus.
- [Tom Servo] I got pudding
in the big white place.
- [Mike] Kinda
embarrassing, really.
Mikey beat me up.
- This one's on the house.
- Thank you Marty.
- Hey gang, look,
who's given credit.
(laughing)
- [Crow] I don't get it.
- Just for him. And just today.
(booing in the crowd)
- [Tom Servo] It's great
how a serial killer
can bring a town together. Huh?
- I'll set it up for everybody.
(cheering)
- [Mike] You just
stay out of the shot.
- And I'll dance with you.
Later.
- [Tom Servo] Dancing,
what to dancing?
- [Crow] Haha, I'm dancing.
- [Tom Servo] This must be
the Yikes Stripes house mix.
- [Crow] It looks like
he took dance lessons
from Arch Hall Jr.
(yelling in surprise)
(mimicking the music)
- [Tom Servo] Boy, look at
that butt, Bud Williamson.
Oh Danny Dean and
the daredevils.
I hope they died knowing
nobody loved them.
- [Crow] I can't take
my eyes off of...
- [Mike] I just know Mikey
ended up in Andy Warhol factory.
- [Tom Servo] I'm the
new janitor now. Hehe..
- [Mike] So I thought
the strangler was going
to be a teenager, hence the
title, 'Teenage Strangler'.
- [Crow] But he wasn't,
he didn't exactly
strangle teenagers.
Cause that one lady was older.
- [Tom Servo] So why the
title 'Teenage Stranglers'?
- [Mike] That
exactly is my point.
(doors closing)
(laughing)
- This is going to be the
best Thanksgiving break ever.
- Oh you betcha.
I can't wait to get home,
Oh bye Mr. Schlocky.
- Goodbye.
(Mike laughing)
- Goodbye kids.
(piano music)
♪The bell has rung. ♪
♪ School is out. ♪
♪The kids have, all gone home. ♪
♪ All I do is sweep and pout. ♪
♪ I'm left here all alone. ♪
♪ I make sure the
hallways are gleaming. ♪
♪ I keep all the
garbage at bay. ♪
♪ But inside my heart
will be screaming. ♪
♪ How did I end up this way. ♪
♪ I'm a janitor. ♪
♪ A janitor. ♪
♪ I clean up the puke
at your school. ♪
♪ A large fist
full of saw dust. ♪
♪ Is my essential tool. ♪
♪ I'm a janitor. ♪
♪ A janitor. ♪
♪ I start work
early each morn. ♪
♪ I have a drinking problem. ♪
♪ And a large
collection of porn. ♪
♪ I'm a janitor. ♪
♪ A janitor. ♪
♪ I'm looked on as
kind of all leech. ♪
♪ But at least I get
more respect then. ♪
♪ The ones who have to teach. ♪
♪ He's a janitor. ♪
♪ A janitor. ♪
♪ Please don't sell him short. ♪
♪ If you get him to mad. ♪
♪ I'll show you my
disgusting wart. ♪
♪ He's a janitor. -
Yeah I'm a janitor. ♪
♪ A janitor. - You got
a problem with that? ♪
♪ He needs to be
loved and respected. ♪
♪ He ones dated
Josephine, the plumber. ♪
♪ And guess what? ♪
♪ Yeah, I was rejected. ♪
♪ He's a janitor. - A janitor. ♪
♪ A janitor. - Yeah
I'm a janitor. ♪
♪ We both think
he's pretty keen. ♪
♪ I hope you liked
our presentation. ♪
♪ Now back to Deep 13.♪
- ♪What do you think sir? ♪
- Oh, good one Mike.
Frank was swaying here
to your little song there
and got sick.
How sick?
That's your dinner for the
next three weeks Frank.
(computer shutting down)
(ending music)
- And he didn't steal
no bike neither, I did.